Now, let's see how to update the elements into two the array, first of all, we have and to add to
the array an integer to the array that is two rows and four columns.
So we need this as created in the previous video.
So please go back to the previous video and see how we have created that array.
This is the array stored in the numbers one two three four, five, six, seven and eight.
And we need to update the elements.
It's very easy to update elements.
It's just like an ordinary array with a single dimension.
It's just specifying the index of the element that you are going to update the element inside it.
OK.
So we are specifying the index of the array element at one and two.
This means that we are working on the second row of index one, which is the second row, and that index
of the column, which is to.
Which is the third column.
OK.
So please guys, think about what we are making here.
We are updating the element and the second row and third column, which is seven.
They think it was ninety nine.
OK.
This is very simple, and it took a time complexity as of one, because we have a direct access to that
array.
And this is the very big and very big advantages of array on other data structures that fit that, like
the easy way to access elements and update elements inside the array.
OK.
So this is how we update elements into two.